A Register of the Stephen J. Tonsor Papers
Hoover Institution Archives
Stephen J. Tonsor Papers
1951-2001
2000C97
Hoover Institution Archives
48 manuscript boxes, 1 oversize box (18.8 linear feet)
Papers of the American historian include correspondence, speeches, and writings, relating to conservative political thought and higher education in the United States.
Tonsor, Stephen J. (Stephen John), 1923-
Access
The collection is open for research
Access to audiovisual materials requires at least two weeks advance notice. Audiovisual materials include sound recordings, video recordings, and motion picture film. Hoover staff will determine whether use copies of the materials requested can be made available. Some materials may not be accessible even with advance notice. Please contact the Hoover Institution Archives for further information.
Acquisition Information
Materials were acquired by the Hoover Institution Archives in 2002
Accruals
Materials may have been added to the collection since this finding aid was prepared. To determine if this has occurred, find the collection in Stanford University's online catalog Socrates at http://library.stanford.edu/webcat. Materials have been added to the collection if the number of boxes listed in Socrates is larger than the number of boxes listed in this finding aid.
Biography Note
1923 November 26 Born, Jerseyville, Illinois
1941-1943 Student, Blackburn College, Carlinville, Illinois
1943-1946 Served as Sergeant (Cryptographer) Signal Corps, U.S. Army
1948 B.A., Philosophy, University of Illinois
1948-1949 Student, University of Zurich, Switzerland
1953-1954 Student, University of Munich, West Germany
1954 Awarded Ph.D., History, University of Illinois
1954- Assistant professor to professor of history, University of Michigan
1954-1955 Pre-doctoral instructor, University of Michigan
1957, 1962, 1972 Horace H. Rackham grantee
1955-1959 Instructor, University of Michigan
1959 Author, National Socialism: Conservative Reaction or Nihilist Revolt?
1959-1964 Assistant professor, University of Michigan
1962 Recipient, University of Michigan Literary and Education Class of 1923 Award for Distinguished Teaching
1962-1963 Relm Foundation grantee
1964- Associate professor, University of Michigan
1969 Associate Editor, Modern Age
1970-1973 Consultant, President's Council of Economic Advisers, Washington, D.C.
1971 Summer grantee, Earhart Foundation
1972 Awarded honorary D. Litt
1972-1973 Research Fellow, Hoover Institution, Stanford University
1974 Author, Tradition and Reform in Education Member, Mont Pelerin Society
1974-1977 Member, board of directors, YM-YWCA, Ann Arbor, Michigan
1975 Author, America's Continuing Revolution: An Act of Conservation
1982 Author, Freedom, Order, and the University
1990 Author, Reflections on the French Revolution: A Hillsdale Symposium
1993 Author, Quest for Liberty: America in Acton's Thought
Scope and Content of Collection
The Stephen John Tonsor papers, acquired in 2002, consist of correspondence, speeches and writings and other materials relating to conservative political thought and to higher education in the United States.
The bulk of the materials contained in the Correspondence series include Stephen Tonsor's personal correspondence with his friends and family members, various organizations he was associated with, and exchange of official letters with his colleagues relating to students' requests for recommendations for teaching positions and admission to graduate programs in different universities around the country. Among his personal correspondents, special mention should be made of, F. A. Hayek, Sidney Hook, Henry Regnery, and Eric Voegelin. Speeches and Writings reflect his political ideas relating to conservative ideology, his views about current educational systems and problems arising out of that system. Some of Henry Regnery's writings are included in the Writings by Others series.
The inclusion of photographs sent to him by his friends, such as Annelise Thimme, George Tilton, and others, complement the series previously mentioned.
Arrangement
The collection is organized into eight series: Biographical File, Correspondence, Speeches and Writings, University of Michigan File, Writings by Others, Subject File, Oversize Material, Photographs
Conservatism.; Education--United States.; United States--Politics and government.; Universities and colleges--United States.
- Biographical File, 1965-1997 and undated. (Box 1)
  Scope and Contents note
  Award, clippings, printed matter, and miscellany relating to Stephen Tonsor's career, arranged alphabetically by physical form
  - Award, Fellowship Program in Economic Education and Administration, 1965; biographical sketch, Who's Who in America, and related material; and curriculum vitae, undated (Folder 1: 1)
  - Clippings, 1971-1991 (Folder 1: 2)
  - Printed matter
    - undated (Folder 1: 3)
    - 1965-1997 (Folder 1: 4-8)
  - Miscellany, 1967-1997 (Box-folder 2: 1-2)
- Correspondence, 1946-1998 and undated.
  General note
  See also Subject File
  Letters sent and received by Stephen Tonsor, including individuals, groups, and organizations, arranged alphabetically by name of correspondent or organization
  Includes related materials such as articles, clippings, memoranda, notes, and miscellany.
  - General
    - undated (Folder 2: 3)
    - 1962-1996 (Folder 2: 4-5)
  - Aaseng, Rolf E., 1971 (Folder 2: 6)
  - Abbema, Loren Van, 1966 (Folder 2: 7)
  - Abraham, David, 1983 (Folder 2: 8)
  - Ackermann, Theodor, 1958-1959 (Folder 2: 9)
  - Adams, Geoffrey, 1970 (Folder 2: 10)
  - Adams, Nora, 1965 (Folder 2: 11)
  - Aggarwal, Arjun P., 1970 (Folder 2: 12)
  - Agnew, Spiro, 1970 (Folder 2: 13)
  - Agria, John J., 1974 (Folder 2: 14)
  - Akufo, Emmanuel, 1970 (Folder 2: 15)
  - Aldridge, Alexandra B., 1974 (Folder 2: 16)
  - Alexander, Eleanor E., 1991 (Folder 2: 17)
  - Alexander, Paul J., 1969-1970 (Folder 2: 18)
  - Allen, William B., 1985 (Folder 2: 19)
  - Allin, Mary Ann, 1983 (Folder 2: 20)
  - Alter, Allan E., 1980 (Folder 2: 21)
  - Altholz, Josef L., 1968-1971 (Folder 2: 22)
  - Altman, William C., 1980 (Folder 2: 23)
  - Alvis, John, 1995 (Folder 2: 24)
  - Amato, Joe, 1966-1990 (Folder 2: 25)
  - American Catholic Historical Association, 1963-1986. (Box-folder 3: 1)
    See also Robert Trisco
  - American Museum of Natural History, 1987 (Folder 3: 2)
  - Amick, Jean, undated (Folder 3: 3)
  - Amidon, Ervan L., 1970 (Folder 3: 4)
  - Anderson, Dennis L., 1975-1981 (Folder 3: 5)
  - Anderson, Frank R., 1971 (Folder 3: 6)
  - Anderson, James B., 1969 (Folder 3: 7)
  - Anderson, Lauren, undated (Folder 3: 8)
  - Anderson, Oscar A., 1969 (Folder 3: 9)
  - Ann Arbor News, 1969 (Folder 3: 10)
  - Annunziata, Frank, 1989 (Folder 3: 11)
  - Appleby, John T., 1970 (Folder 3: 12)
  - Arca, Emil, 1984 (Folder 3: 13)
  - Arlotto, William D., 1986-1987 (Folder 3: 14)
  - Arnheim, Rudolf, 1981 (Folder 3: 15)
  - Arny, Wayne, 1980 (Folder 3: 16)
  - Art Institute of Chicago, 1985 (Folder 3: 17)
  - Arthos, John, 1970 (Folder 3: 18)
  - Ascher, Abraham, 1974 (Folder 3: 19)
  - Ash, Robert, 1974 (Folder 3: 20)
  - Augenstein, Leroy G., 1969 (Folder 3: 21)
  - Augros, Robert M., 1983 (Folder 3: 22)
  - Ayres, James H., circa 1971 (Folder 3: 23)
  - Babione, Daisy, Mrs., 1971 (Folder 3: 24)
  - Bailey, Charles, 1985. (Folder 3: 25)
    See also Thomas T. Tentler
  - Bailey, Richard W., 1984 (Folder 3: 26)
  - Baldwin, John, 1967 (Folder 3: 27)
  - Balla, Phil, 1970-1971 (Folder 3: 28)
  - Balog, James T., 1970 (Folder 3: 29)
  - Balogh, Sandor, 1983 (Folder 3: 30)
  - Bambach, Charles
    - undated (Folder 3: 31)
    - 1976-1990 (Folder 3: 32)
    - 1991-1997 (Folder 3: 33)
  - Bankmann, Ulf, 1985 (Folder 3: 34)
  - Bargad, Warren, 1983 (Folder 3: 35)
  - Barker, Stanley Cline, circa 1969 (Folder 3: 36)
  - Barletta, William L., 1965 (Folder 3: 37)
  - Barnes, William E. O., 1968 (Folder 3: 38)
  - Barnett, Frank R., 1969 (Folder 3: 39)
  - Barney, Joseph A., 1974 (Folder 3: 40)
  - Baroody, William Joseph Jr., Mr. and Mrs.
    - 1969-1975 (Folder 3: 41)
    - 1976-1984 (Folder 3: 42)
  - Barry, Edward, 1981 (Folder 3: 43)
  - Bate, George L., 1975 (Folder 3: 44)
  - Bateman, Lewis, 1980-1984 (Folder 3: 45)
  - Bauer, Peter, 1974 (Box-folder 4: 1)
  - Baxter, Hugh, 1979 (Folder 4: 2)
  - Bay, Christian, 1971 (Folder 4: 3)
  - Beale, Walter, 1985 (Folder 4: 4)
  - Beaumont, William, 1967-1969 and undated (Folder 4: 5)
  - Beisner, Robert L., 1985 (Folder 4: 6)
  - Belgray, Alice B., 1970 (Folder 4: 7)
  - Bell, Daniel, 1982 (Folder 4: 8)
  - Bell, L. Nelson, 1970 (Folder 4: 9)
  - Benedict, Philip, 1986 (Folder 4: 10)
  - Benford, Harry, 1970 (Folder 4: 11)
  - Benson, George C. S., 1969 (Folder 4: 12)
  - Benson, Joan, 1989 (Folder 4: 13)
  - Berberet, William G., 1987-1988 (Folder 4: 14)
  - Berg, Meredith, 1986 (Folder 4: 15)
  - Berger, Peter L., 1968-1979 (Folder 4: 16)
  - Berman, Ronald S., 1974-1975 (Folder 4: 17)
  - Bernard, Richard M., 1984 (Folder 4: 18)
  - Berquist, Marcus, 1974 (Folder 4: 19)
  - Berry, Charles, 1986 (Folder 4: 20)
  - Bertier, G. de, undated (Folder 4: 21)
  - Betanzos, Kathleen, 1998 (Folder 4: 22)
  - Betanzos, Ramon J., 1966-1989 (Folder 4: 23)
  - Biederwolf, Robert, 1969-1970 (Folder 4: 24)
  - Bierly, Ivan R., 1964 (Folder 4: 25)
  - Billick, Dave, 1983 (Folder 4: 26)
  - Binkley, Thomas, 1973 (Folder 4: 27)
  - Birr, Kendall, 1967 (Folder 4: 28)
  - Bishirjian, Richard J., 1971-1986 (Folder 4: 29)
  - Bitting, Christina, 1966-1968 (Folder 4: 30)
  - Black, Bruce Douglas, 1968 (Folder 4: 31)
  - Blackburn, Robert T., 1973 (Folder 4: 32)
  - Blackwell, Gordon W., 1970 (Folder 4: 33)
  - Blair, C. Stanley, 1970 (Folder 4: 34)
  - Bleiberg, Robert M., 1970 (Folder 4: 35)
  - Block, Walter, 1982-1983 (Folder 4: 36)
  - Bloomhardt, R. J., Mr. and Mrs., 1982-1988 and undated (Folder 4: 37)
  - Blum, Albert A., 1970 (Folder 4: 38)
  - Boarman, Patrick M., 1996 (Folder 4: 39)
  - Bodman, Henry T., 1969-1974 and undated (Folder 4: 40)
  - Bodman, Weezie?, undated (Folder 4: 41)
  - Bolduc, Thomas E., 1970 (Folder 4: 42)
  - Bolen, Charles W., 1971 (Folder 4: 43)
  - Bolstler, Elizabeth, 1982 (Folder 4: 44)
  - Boorstin, Daniel J., 1970 (Folder 4: 45)
  - Booth, Wayne C., 1989. (Folder 4: 46)
    See also Henry Regnery
  - Borgquist, Daryl, 1984 (Folder 4: 47)
  - Borkman, Kurt J., 1985-1993 and undated (Folder 4: 48)
  - Bovenizer, David A., 1996 (Folder 4: 49)
  - Bowers, Robert E., 1970 (Folder 4: 50)
  - Bowsma, William J., 1970 (Folder 4: 51)
  - Boyd, Jonathan, 1992 (Folder 4: 52)
  - Bozell, L. Brent, 1970 (Folder 4: 53)
  - Bradford, M. E., 1971-1986 (Folder 4: 54)
  - Bradley, Robert I., 1970 (Folder 4: 55)
  - Brady, Thomas A., Jr., 1983 (Folder 4: 56)
  - Brandin, G. Rudolph, 1974 (Folder 4: 57)
  - Branham, Jill M., 1992 (Folder 4: 58)
  - Brann, Eva, 1985-1989 (Folder 4: 59)
  - Bray, Thomas J., undated (Folder 4: 60)
  - Breckenridge, Joe, undated (Folder 4: 61)
  - Breihan, J. R., 1984 (Folder 4: 62)
  - Brewer, Thomas B., 1971 (Folder 4: 63)
  - Brezicki, Margaret M., 1987 (Folder 4: 64)
  - Briefs, Goetz, 1970 (Folder 4: 65)
  - Brink, James E., 1983-1984 (Folder 4: 66)
  - Brinkley, George, 1971 (Folder 4: 67)
  - Brinks, Herbert, 1975 (Folder 4: 68)
  - Briscoe, Keith G., 1972 (Folder 4: 69)
  - Brodt, Carl L., 1973 (Folder 4: 70)
  - Broek, William Vanden, 1969 (Folder 4: 71)
  - Brooks, Samuel M., 1982 (Folder 4: 72)
  - Brown, Gaylen, 1969 (Box-folder 5: 1)
  - Brown, Harry E., 1974 and undated (Folder 5: 2)
  - Brown, Kay, 1984-1985 (Folder 5: 3)
  - Brown, Kendall W., 1983 (Folder 5: 4)
  - Brunsdale, Anne, 1975 (Folder 5: 5)
  - Brushaber, George K., 1970 (Folder 5: 6)
  - Bryant, T. C., 1971 (Folder 5: 7)
  - Buckler, John, 1988 (Folder 5: 8)
  - Buckley, Priscilla L., 1969-1973 (Folder 5: 9)
  - Buckley, William F., Jr., 1965-1991 (Folder 5: 10)
  - Bullock, Henry M., 1970 (Folder 5: 11)
  - Bunting, Robert, 1981-1982 (Folder 5: 12)
  - Burleigh, Anne, 1984 (Folder 5: 13)
  - Burns, Norman, 1971 (Folder 5: 14)
  - Burrows, E. G., 1969 (Folder 5: 15)
  - Bush, John W, 1970 (Folder 5: 16)
  - Butler, Jeffrey, 1985 (Folder 5: 17)
  - Butterfield, Herbert, 1951 (Folder 5: 18)
  - Byers, Walter, 1969 (Folder 5: 19)
  - Byrd, R. Eugene, 1971 (Folder 5: 20)
  - Cali, Christian R., 1994 (Folder 5: 21)
  - Cambridge University Press, 1970 (Folder 5: 22)
  - Campaigne, Jameson G., Jr., 1966-1986 (Folder 5: 23)
  - Campbell, Angus, 1970 (Folder 5: 24)
  - Campbell, Bill, 1996 (Folder 5: 25)
  - Campbell, William F., 1969-1995 and undated (Folder 5: 26)
  - Cansler, Loman D., 1970 (Folder 5: 27)
  - Capaldi, Nicholas, 1984-1992 (Folder 5: 28)
  - Caponigri, A. Robert, 1970 (Folder 5: 29)
  - Carey, Christopher R., 1969-1970 (Folder 5: 30)
  - Carey, George W., 1970-1971 (Folder 5: 31)
  - Carlson, Allan C., 1990 (Folder 5: 32)
  - Carlson, Edgar M., 1970 (Folder 5: 33)
  - Carlsson, Eric, 1991-1994 (Folder 5: 34)
  - Carneal, Jeffrey J., 1994 (Folder 5: 35)
  - Carson, Thomas E., 1983 (Folder 5: 36)
  - Carter, Richard B., 1980 (Folder 5: 37)
  - Cartier, Louis F., Jr., 1977 (Folder 5: 38)
  - Carus, M. Blouke, 1993 (Folder 5: 39)
  - Case, David T., 1980 (Folder 5: 40)
  - Case, Elisabeth W., 1965-1968 (Folder 5: 41)
  - Catholic Historical Review, 1973-1988. (Folder 5: 42)
  - Catholic University of America, 1974-1981 (Folder 5: 43)
  - Catholicism in Crisis, 1986 (Folder 5: 44)
  - Catholics of Economic Growth, 1987 (Folder 5: 45)
  - Cavanaugh, Tom, Mrs., 1970 (Folder 5: 46)
  - Center for Economic and Policy Education, 1996-1997 (Folder 5: 47)
  - Chaet, Alfred B., 1968 (Folder 5: 48)
  - Chalmers, Mary E., 1985 and undated (Folder 5: 49)
  - Chamberlain, John, 1971 (Folder 5: 50)
  - Chickering, A. Lawrence, 1986 (Folder 5: 51)
  - Chilman, Walter J., 1986 (Folder 5: 52)
  - Chitester, Robert J., 1985-1986 (Folder 5: 53)
  - Christensen, George C., 1975 (Folder 5: 54)
  - Christian Science Monitor, 1980-1981 (Folder 5: 55)
  - Christian Scholar's Review, 1970 (Folder 5: 56)
  - Christmann, Adam, 1977 (Folder 5: 57)
  - Chrobot, Leonard F., 1971 (Folder 5: 58)
  - Clare, George, 1967 (Folder 5: 59)
  - Clark, William Reeve, 1969-1970 (Folder 5: 60)
  - Clor, Harry M., 1970-1973 and undated (Folder 5: 61)
  - Coakley, Frank, 1968-1969 (Folder 5: 62)
  - Cobb, Jean Danzer, 1975 (Folder 5: 63)
  - Cockip, Chez M., 1978 (Folder 5: 64)
  - Cogan, Marc, 1986 (Folder 5: 65)
  - Cohen, Wilbur J., 1970 (Box-folder 6: 1)
  - Colby, Roy, 1971 (Folder 6: 2)
  - Cole, John R., 1984 (Folder 6: 3)
  - Coleson, Edward P., 1967-1968 (Folder 6: 4)
  - Collier, David S.
    - 1964-1971 (Folder 6: 5)
    - 1972-1983 (Folder 6: 6)
  - Committee for the Bicentennial, 1971-1975 (Folder 6: 7)
  - Comprone, Joseph J., 1990 (Folder 6: 8)
  - Connolly, Ruth E., 1994-1997 (Folder 6: 9)
  - Cony, Edward R., 1971 (Folder 6: 10)
  - Cooke, Romney W., 1971 (Folder 6: 11)
  - Cooley, Janet, 1982 (Folder 6: 12)
  - Cooper, George E., Jr.
    - 1968-1977 (Folder 6: 13)
    - 1978-1984 (Folder 6: 14)
  - Cooper, John W., 1980-1981 (Folder 6: 15)
  - Cope, J. I., 1956 (Folder 6: 16)
  - Coriden, Guy E., 1968 (Folder 6: 17)
  - Cornell Alumni Committee for Balanced Education, 1960-1972. (Folder 6: 18)
    Includes J. D. Tuller
  - Cornell University Press, 1966 (Folder 6: 19)
  - Corpus Dictionaries, 1969 and undated (Folder 6: 20)
  - Corwin, Rebecca Brown, 1971 (Folder 6: 21)
  - Cory, Mary?, 1987 (Folder 6: 22)
  - Cosner, Mary, 1984-1989 (Folder 6: 23)
  - Coston, Herbert, 1983 (Folder 6: 24)
  - Cotton, W. Philip, Jr., 1968 (Folder 6: 25)
  - Covent, Jane, undated (Folder 6: 26)
  - Cox, Billy Ray, 1967-1975 (Folder 6: 27)
  - Cox, Eugene L., 1975 (Folder 6: 28)
  - Crane, Philip M., 1978 (Folder 6: 29)
  - Creech, Jill, undated (Folder 6: 30)
  - Cribb, Kenneth, Jr., 1972 (Folder 6: 31)
  - Cribb, T. Kenneth, Jr., 1978 (Folder 6: 32)
  - Criscuolo, Antonio T., 1970 (Folder 6: 33)
  - Croake, Richard, 1971 (Folder 6: 34)
  - Cronin, Morton, 1972 (Folder 6: 35)
  - Crosson, Frederick J., 1981 (Box-folder 7: 1)
  - Crowder, C., 1983 (Folder 7: 2)
  - Culross, Rita R., 1988 (Folder 7: 3)
  - Curry, Richard C., 1969 (Folder 7: 4)
  - Cutler, Richard L., 1972-1993 (Folder 7: 5)
  - Cutsinger, Carol, 1995 (Folder 7: 6)
  - Cutsinger, James S., 1994 (Folder 7: 7)
  - D'Andrea, Tom, 1993 (Folder 7: 8)
  - D'Arms, John H., 1985-1987 (Folder 7: 9)
  - D'Souza, Dinesh, 1981 and undated (Folder 7: 10)
  - D. Van Nostrand Company, Inc., 1967 (Folder 7: 11)
  - Dahl, John R., 1982 (Folder 7: 12)
  - Daly, Joseph S., 1986 (Folder 7: 13)
  - Dannhauser, Werner J., 1986 (Folder 7: 14)
  - Dante,?, 1992 (Folder 7: 15)
  - Davidoff, Norma, 1971 (Folder 7: 16)
  - Davidson, Eugene, 1963-1968 (Folder 7: 17)
  - Davis, Belinda, 1985 (Folder 7: 18)
  - Davis, John E., 1986 (Folder 7: 19)
  - Davis, Matthew M., 1991 (Folder 7: 20)
  - Davies, William, 1985 (Folder 7: 21)
  - Dawson, Christopher, 1959 (Folder 7: 22)
  - Dearborn Rotary Club, 1970 (Folder 7: 23)
  - Decker, Fred W., 1970 (Folder 7: 24)
  - Decter, Moshe, 1972 (Folder 7: 25)
  - Deitenbeck, Bill, Jr., 1970 (Folder 7: 26)
  - Delehanty, William, 1985 (Folder 7: 27)
  - DeLuca, Peter L., 1965 (Folder 7: 28)
  - DeMatteis, Rosalind, 1967 (Folder 7: 29)
  - Denman, William F., 1983-1988 (Folder 7: 30)
  - Dennis, William C., 1985-1988 (Folder 7: 31)
  - Derrick, Christopher, 1970-1971 (Folder 7: 32)
  - Dervishi, Brian S., 1977-1992 and undated (Folder 7: 33)
  - Devlin, Barbara A., 1975 (Folder 7: 34)
  - Diamond, Martin, 1975 (Folder 7: 35)
  - Dickman, Howard, 1980 (Folder 7: 36)
  - Dickson, Peter W., 1970-1980 (Folder 7: 37)
  - Die President, Johannesburg, 1969 (Folder 7: 38)
  - Die Welt, 1966 (Folder 7: 39)
  - Dodds, Andy C., 1978-1981 (Folder 7: 40)
  - Dodson, Ken, 1968 (Folder 7: 41)
  - Dodt, Jeffrey A., 1984 (Folder 7: 42)
  - Doenecke, Carol, 1985 (Folder 7: 43)
  - Doenecke, Justus D., 1984-1989 (Folder 7: 44)
  - Doeringer, F. M., 1984 (Folder 7: 45)
  - Donald, Aida DiPace, 1973 (Folder 7: 46)
  - Donnelly, Mark Anthony, 1994 (Folder 7: 47)
  - Donovan, Michael A., 1975 (Folder 7: 48)
  - Dotson, Paul R., 1970 (Folder 7: 49)
  - Dott, Diane, 1994 (Folder 7: 50)
  - Dougherty, Jude P., 1974-1980 (Folder 7: 51)
  - Dougherty, Richard M., 1987 (Folder 7: 52)
  - Dowling, Lester M., 1966 (Folder 7: 53)
  - Downey, Betsy, 1987 (Folder 7: 54)
  - Dudden, Arthur P., 1982 (Folder 7: 55)
  - Duke, Kathleen F., 1991 (Folder 7: 56)
  - Dumm, Christine, 1997 (Folder 7: 57)
  - Dunbar, Willis, 1968 (Folder 7: 58)
  - Dunlap, Beth, undated (Folder 7: 59)
  - Durant, William Clark III, 1970 (Folder 7: 60)
  - Dwyer, Robert J., 1968-1970 and undated (Folder 7: 61)
  - Dykes, E. W., 1969 (Folder 7: 62)
  - Eadie, John, 1969 (Folder 7: 63)
  - Ecclestone, David A., 1969 (Folder 7: 64)
  - Edelen, Stephen R., 1983 (Folder 7: 65)
  - Edwards, Lee, 1970 (Folder 7: 66)
  - Ege, Nezahet Nurettin, 1944-1984 (Folder 7: 67)
  - Eggert, Linda, 1975 (Folder 7: 68)
  - Ehmann, John, 1967 (Folder 7: 69)
  - Ehrmann, Howard M., 1954-1956 (Folder 7: 70)
  - Ekman, Richard H., 1975 (Folder 7: 71)
  - Elsas, Norman E., 1970 (Box-folder 8: 1)
  - Else, Gerald F., 1966 (Folder 8: 2)
  - Elsert, Katherine, undated (Folder 8: 3)
  - Epstein, Fritz T., 1967 (Folder 8: 4)
  - Epstein, Klaus, 1966 (Folder 8: 5)
  - Ericson, Edward E. III, Jr., 1974-1976 and undated (Folder 8: 6)
  - Ericson, Stephen A., 1984 and undated (Folder 8: 7)
  - Erlich, John L., 1970 (Folder 8: 8)
  - Esch, Marvin L., 1968-1971 (Folder 8: 9)
  - Etter, Brian, 1984-1994 and undated. (Folder 8: 10)
    See also Charles Bambach
  - Evans, Lyon, 1974-1975 (Folder 8: 11)
  - Evans, M. Stanton, 1970-1982 (Folder 8: 12)
  - Eyck, U. Frank J., 1985 (Folder 8: 13)
  - Faberman, Hilarie, 1986 (Folder 8: 14)
  - Fallis, Laurence S., 1970 (Folder 8: 15)
  - Fand, David I., 1990 (Folder 8: 16)
  - Fanning, Louis, 1981 (Folder 8: 17)
  - Farmer, Christopher, 1978-1988 (Folder 8: 18)
  - Farnham, Nicholas, 1978 (Folder 8: 19)
  - Fears, J. Rufus, 1983-1992 and undated (Folder 8: 20)
  - Feigenbaum, Susan, 1991 (Folder 8: 21)
  - Feinberg, Charles E., 1961 (Folder 8: 22)
  - Feldman, Gerald D., 1975 (Folder 8: 23)
  - Feldman, Marlene, 1971 (Folder 8: 24)
  - Fenyo, Robert P., 1968-1971 (Folder 8: 25)
  - Fettig, John M., 1988 (Folder 8: 26)
  - Feuerwerker, Albert, 1984-1985 (Folder 8: 27)
  - Feulner, Edwin J., Jr., 1971-1985 and undated (Folder 8: 28)
  - Fielczak, John J., 1978 (Folder 8: 29)
  - Filler, Louis, 1986 (Folder 8: 30)
  - Finch, Robert H., 1970 (Folder 8: 31)
  - Fine, Sidney, 1971 (Folder 8: 32)
  - Fingerhut, Bruce M., 1976 (Folder 8: 33)
  - Fink, John, 1966 (Folder 8: 34)
  - Fishbane, Jon, 1980-1987 and undated (Folder 8: 35)
  - Fitzpatrick, Sheila, 1983 (Folder 8: 36)
  - Fitzsimons, M. A., 1971 (Folder 8: 37)
  - Fleming, Robben W., 1969-1971 and undated (Folder 8: 38)
  - Flickner, Charles, 1966 (Folder 8: 39)
  - Florer, John H., 1971 (Folder 8: 40)
  - Foote, Susan, 1968-1969 and undated (Folder 8: 41)
  - Forbes, Anthony H., 1967-1968 (Folder 8: 42)
  - Ford Foundation, 1970 (Folder 8: 43)
  - Ford, Gerald R., 1965-1967 (Folder 8: 44)
  - Fort Hays Kansas State College, 1971 (Folder 8: 45)
  - Foster, Mary C., 1970 and undated (Folder 8: 46)
  - Fowler, Booth, 1969 (Folder 8: 47)
  - Fox, Patricia M., 1965 (Folder 8: 48)
  - Fox, Robert S., 1967 (Folder 8: 49)
  - Fox, Robert W., 1968-1969 (Folder 8: 50)
  - Francis, Samuel T., 1984 (Folder 8: 51)
  - Franck, Michael, 1971 (Folder 8: 52)
  - Freedom House, 1983 (Folder 8: 53)
  - Freimuth, E. G., 1970 (Folder 8: 54)
  - Frick, Charlotte, 1988 (Folder 8: 55)
  - Frischer(?) Bernard D., 1971 (Folder 8: 56)
  - Froehlke, Bruce, 1986-1987 (Folder 8: 57)
  - Fry, David E., 1970 (Folder 8: 58)
  - Frye, B. E., 1974-1980 (Folder 8: 59)
  - Fuller, Edmund, 1980 (Box-folder 9: 1)
  - Fuller, Timothy, 1989 (Folder 9: 2)
  - Fund for Theological Education, 1968 (Folder 9: 3)
  - Furet(?), Francois, undated (Folder 9: 4)
  - Furst, Milton, 1970 (Folder 9: 5)
  - Fusfeld, Dan, 1970 (Folder 9: 6)
  - Gagliano, Joseph A., 1987 (Folder 9: 7)
  - Gajewski, Mary O'Brien, circa 1977 (Folder 9: 8)
  - Galanski, Virginia, undated (Folder 9: 9)
  - Galbreath, Robert and Naomi, 1966-1970 and undated (Folder 9: 10)
  - Gallin, Mary Alice, 1969 (Folder 9: 11)
  - Gamage, Robert D., 1970 (Folder 9: 12)
  - Gammon, Samuel R., 1981 (Folder 9: 13)
  - Ganus, Clifton L., Jr., 1968 (Folder 9: 14)
  - Garmel, Sara, 1981 (Folder 9: 15)
  - Garrison, Garnet R., 1969 (Folder 9: 16)
  - Gaston, James, 1986 (Folder 9: 17)
  - Geiger, Roger L., 1969-1983 (Folder 9: 18)
  - Gelbach, Clyde C., 1970 (Folder 9: 19)
  - General Motors Corporation, 1971 (Folder 9: 20)
  - Genovese, Eugene D., 1969-1975 (Folder 9: 21)
  - George, Emery E., 1971 (Folder 9: 22)
  - Gerber, John M., 1986 (Folder 9: 23)
  - Gerety, Peter, 1975 (Folder 9: 24)
  - German Information Center, 1971 (Folder 9: 25)
  - Gettman, Royal A., 1986 (Folder 9: 26)
  - Gewanter, David, 1980 and undated (Folder 9: 27)
  - Geyer, Michael, 1985-1986 (Folder 9: 28)
  - Gheyn(?), John W., 1986 (Folder 9: 29)
  - Gibson, Charles, 1968 (Folder 9: 30)
  - Gideonse, Harry D., 1969 (Folder 9: 31)
  - Giesecke, G. Ernst, 1971 (Folder 9: 32)
  - Gilbert, Martin, 1989 (Folder 9: 33)
  - Gildner, Jay W., 1981 (Folder 9: 34)
  - Giles, S. F., 1972 (Folder 9: 35)
  - Gill, William J., 1968 (Folder 9: 36)
  - Gillis, John, 1968-1969 (Folder 9: 37)
  - Gillis, Mary, 1992 (Folder 9: 38)
  - Gilman, Sander L., 1984 (Folder 9: 39)
  - Glasse, Jack, 1988 (Folder 9: 40)
  - Gleason, Philip, 1974 (Folder 9: 41)
  - Glen, Robert, 1983-1985 (Folder 9: 42)
  - Glover, M. W., Jr., 1986 (Folder 9: 43)
  - Goldenberg, Edie N., 1994 (Folder 9: 44)
  - Goldman, Bernard M., 1979-1980 (Folder 9: 45)
  - Goodell, Grace E., 1983 and undated (Folder 9: 46)